[{
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 1",
	"question": "How many pairs of cranial nerves do human beings have?",
	"answers": ["c"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "08 pairs",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "10 pairs",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "12 pairs",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "14 pairs",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 2",
	"question": "Where are the cell bodies and the cranial outlet of the olfactory nerve (NC I) located?",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Olfactory epithelium (olfactory cells). Cranial exit through foramina in the nasal bone",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory epithelium (olfactory cells). Cranial exit through foramina in the cribiform lamina of the ethmoid bone",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory epithelium (olfactory cells). Cranial exit through foramina in the cribiform lamina of the sphenoid bone",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory epithelium (olfactory cells). Cranial exit through foramina in zygomatic bone",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 3",
	"question": "Where are the cell bodies and the cranial outlet of the Optic nerve (NCII) located?",
	"answers": ["a"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Retina (ganglion cells). Cranial outlet through the optical channel",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Iris (ganglion cells). Cranial outlet through the optical channel",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Iris (ganglion cells). Cranial exit through the foramen ovale",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Retina (ganglion cells). Cranial exit through the foramen ovale",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 4",
	"question": "Where does the cranial exit from the ocular nerve [motor (NC III) take place?",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "The round foramen",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "By the superior orbital fissure",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "By the lower orbital fissure",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Through the foramen ovale",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 5",
	"question": "Where are the cell bodies and the cranial outlet of the trochlear nerve (NC IV) located?",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Cell bodies in the midbrain. Cranial exit through the round foramen",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Cell bodies in the midbrain. Cranial exit through the superior orbital fissure",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Cell bodies in the diencephalon. Cranial exit through the superior orbital fissure",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Cell bodies in the diencephalon. Cranial exit through the round foramen",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 6",
	"question": "What is the component of the trigeminal nerve and what is the location of their cell bodies?",
	"answers": ["c"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Visceral motor. Trigeminal ganglion",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Somatic engine. Trigeminal ganglion",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "General sensitive. Trigeminal ganglion",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Special sensitive. Trigeminal ganglion",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 7",
	"question": "Where are the cell bodies and the cranial outlet of the Abducente nerve (NC VI) located?",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Bridge. Cranial exit from the stylomatoid foramen",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Bridge. Cranial exit through the superior orbital fissure",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Oblong cord. Cranial exit from the stylomatoid foramen",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Oblong cord. Cranial exit through the superior orbital fissure",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 8",
	"question": "The facial nerve (NC VII) has which fiber components?",
	"answers": ["a"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Motor branchial, special sensitive, general sensitive and visceral motor",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Special sensitive, somatic motor and visceral motor",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "General sensory, somatic motor, and gill motor",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Motor branch, special sensory, somatic motor and visceral motor",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 9",
	"question": "The Vestibulocochlear nerve (NC VIII) is divided into:",
	"answers": ["d"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Vestibular and hearing",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Vestibular and Temporal",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Vestibular and acoustic",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Vestibular and cochlear",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 10",
	"question": "Which glossopharyngeal nerve (NC IX) has nerve fibers of which type, and where does it exit the skull?",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "It has general and special sensitive nerve fibers. The exit of the skull occurs through the foramen magnum",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "It has motor branchial, motor visceral, visceral sensitive, special sensitive and general sensitive nerve fibers. The exit of the skull occurs through the jugular foramen",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Has motor branchial, visceral motor, visceral sensitive, special sensitive and general sensitive nerve fibers. The exit of the skull occurs through the foramen magnum",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "It has general and special sensitive nerve fibers. The exit of the skull occurs through the foramen ovale",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 11",
	"question": "Where does the vagus nerve exit (NC X)?",
	"answers": ["c"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Magnum foramen",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Oval foramen",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Jugular foramen",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Round foramen",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 12",
	"question": "The accessory nerve (NC XI) has two divisions, what are they? Where does the skull exit from them?",
	"answers": ["d"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Cranial and medullary root. Both come out of the skull through the jugular foramen",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Cranial root and spinal root. They leave the skull through the foramen ovale and magnum respectively",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Cranial root and medullary root. Exit through the skull through the foramen ovale and magnum respectively",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Cranial root and spinal root. Both come out of the skull through the jugular foramen",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 13",
	"question": "What type of nerve fiber and what means of exit from the skull of the hypoglossal nerve (NC XII)?",
	"answers": ["a"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Somatic engine. Exit of the skull through the hypoglossal nerve canal",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Motor gill. Exit of the skull through the foramen ovale",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Visceral motor. Exit of the skull through the round foramen",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Special sensitive. Exit of the skull through the jugular foramen",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 14",
	"question": "The trigeminal nerve is divided into three parts, which are:",
	"answers": ["b"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Ophthalmic division, olfactory division and maxillary division",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Ophthalmic division, maxillary division and mandibular division",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory division, ophthalmic division and mandibular division",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory division, maxillary division and mandibular division",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 15",
	"question": "The nerve responsible for vision from the retina is the nerve:",
	"answers": ["d"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Abducente (NC VI)",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Oculomotor (NC III)",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Trochlear (NC IV)",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Optical (NC II)",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 16",
	"question": "Which nerves pass through the internal auditory canal?",
	"answers": ["c"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Abducent Nerve (NC VI) and Trochlear Nerve (NC IV)",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Trochlear Nerve (NC IV) and Optic Nerve (NC II)",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Vestibulocochlear nerve (NC VIII) vestibular and cochlear portion; and branch of the fascial nerve (NC VII)",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Hypoglossal Nerve (NC XII) and Accessory Nerve (NC XI)",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 17",
	"question": "The nerve responsible for the inversion of the tongue muscles (with the exception of the palatoglossus) is:",
	"answers": ["a"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Hypoglossal Nerve (NC XII)",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Abducent Nerve (NC VI)",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Trochlear Nerve (NC IV)",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Accessory Nerve (NC XI)",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 18",
	"question": "Nerve responsible for the odor sensation, and its type of nerve fiber:",
	"answers": ["d"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Olfactory nerve (NCI). General Sensitive",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory nerve (NCI). Visceral engine",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory nerve (NCI). Somatic engine",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Olfactory nerve (NCI). Special Sensitive",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 19",
	"question": "Of the nerves below, which one does not have mixed nerve fibers?",
	"answers": ["a"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Abducent Nerve (NC VI)",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Facial Nerve (NC VII)",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Trigeminal nerve (NC V)",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Glossopharyngeal nerve (NC IX)",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}, {
	"category": "nervos",
	"title": "Question 20",
	"question": "Which of the following nerves do not have special sensitive nerve fibers?",
	"answers": ["c"],
	"options": [{
		"label": "Olfactory Nerve (NC I)",
		"value": "a"
	}, {
		"label": "Optic Nerve (NC II)",
		"value": "b"
	}, {
		"label": "Accessory Nerve (NC XI)",
		"value": "c"
	}, {
		"label": "Vestibulocochlear Nerve (NC VIII)",
		"value": "d"
	}]
}]